再见  John
Good-bye, john.
你要对他们撒谎
You're gonna have to lie.
这是唯一能保护它的办法
It's the only way to protect it.
这只是个岛  John
It's an island, john.
没有人需要保护它
No one needs to protect it.
这是个奇迹发生的地方
It's a place where miracles happen.
世上根本就没有奇迹
There's no such thing as miracles.
我们得把所有多余的东西
We gotta get every ounce of extra weight
扔下去
Off this chopper now!
所有没用的东西  都扔下去
Anything that's not bolted down, toss it out!
Sawyer
Sawyer!
能把一艘航母炸掉
To blow up a bloody aircraft carrier.
这是个收音机
This is a-a radio receiver.
就会远程引爆炸弹
it triggers the bomb remotely.
我已经投了一份人身保? Ben
I took out a bit of a-a life insurance policy, ben.
你杀了我的女儿
You killed my daughter.
你杀了那船上的所有人
You just killed everybody on that boat.
那又怎么?
So?
声明：本字幕由YYeTs人人影视字幕组原创翻译制作
禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎登录人人影视论坛交流 下载 在线观看 www.YYeTs.net
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：小帝 66 战 螃蟹 思思 paradise 妞妞
校对：何何 思思 螃蟹 战 美景 小帝时间轴：YY吕伟 leolou
========== 字幕总监制：何何   ==========
对不起  先生  不好意思打搅你一下
Excuse me, sir. I'm sorry to bother you.
请问现在几点了?
But do you have the time, please?
8点50...
Yeah. it's eight fif--
Sayid?
你好  Hurley
Hello, hurley.
探访时间已经过了吧  老兄
I think visiting hours are over, dude.
我不是来看你的
This isn't a visit.
我要你跟我走
I want you to come with me.
跟你去哪里?
Come with you where?
一个安全的地方
Somewhere safe.
我干嘛要跟你走啊?
And why would I go anywhere with you?
我貌似有N久没有见过你了
I haven't seen you in, like, forever.
因为情况有变
Because circumstances have changed.
什么样的情况?
What circumstances?
Bentham死了
Bentham's dead.
什么
What?
两天前死的
Two days ago.
发生什么事了?
What happened?
据说他是自杀
They said it was suicide.
什么叫"据说"他是自杀?
What do you mean, they "said" it was suicide?
-还有你干嘛叫他"Bentham"?  他名叫...  -别说出来
- And why are you calling him "bentham"? his name is-- don't say it.
我们被监视了
We're being watched.
老兄  我一直在
Dude, I've been having
和死人聊着天
Regular conversations with dead people.
我准是有妄想症
The last thing I need now is paranoia.
我刚杀了一个从上星期起
I just killed a man who's been perched
就守在门外的家伙
Outside this facility for the last week.
我就是全靠妄想症而得以生存至今
I'm finding paranoia keeps me alive.
我们不是要回去吧?
We're not going back, are we?
不是
No.
只是去个安全的地方
Just somewhere safe.
那好吧
Okay then.
等一下
Hold on a sec.
将死  Eko先生
Checkmate, mr. eko.
-货船在哪  -我也不知道  我保持着正确航向
- Where's the freighter? -  I don't know.  I stayed on course.
他们一定又是把船开走了
They must have it on the move again.
还剩多少油?
How much fuel?
还能坚持4到5分钟
Four, five minutes worth,
除非还有人想跳下去减轻负荷
Unless somebody else wants to jump.
我们一找到船就折回去找他
As soon as we get to the boat, we'll go back for him.
船在那儿! 我看到了! 就在我们后面!
There it is! the boat! I see it! behind us!
Ben  帮帮我
Ben, help me.
要是他死了  船上的人就都得玩完了
If he dies, everybody on that boat dies.
那可不关我的事  John
That's not my problem, john.
挺住  挺住!
Hang on, man. hang on!
不管你逃到天涯海角...
Wherever you go...
Widmore...
都会上门来找你算帐的
He'll find you.
没准我先找他算帐呢
Not if I find him first.
不要啊  不要
Hey. no. no.
你们俩现在就走  让所有人都离开船
You two need to go now. get everybody off the boat.
瓶里大概还剩5分钟左右的冷冻气体
We have maybe five minutes left in the tank.
走啊!
Go!
你走  快走
You go. go.
我留下来
I stay.
糟糕
Oh, bloody hell.
别着陆!
Don't land!
你们不能着陆!  别着陆!
You can't land! don't land!
别着陆!
Don't land!
要爆炸了!　要爆炸了!
There's a bomb! there's a bomb!
快离开啊! 要爆炸了!
Get away! there's a bomb!
-你们不能着陆! 飞回去! -他是不是说"要爆炸了"?
You can't land! go back! did he say "bomb"?
别着陆!
Don't land!
-你在干嘛?!  -我才不管他在嚷嚷什么!
What are you doing?! I don't care what the hell he's screaming!
飞机都冒烟了!  我必须让这铁家伙着陆!
I'm flying on fumes! I gotta put this bird down!
不要!  别着陆!
No! don't land!
不!  不!  你不明白!
No! no! look, you don't understand!
Jin和Michael在尽一切力量
Jin and michael are doing everything they can,
可是没时间了!
But there's no time!
你们现在都给我下船!
You've gotta get off the boat now!
我们还要多久才能再次起飞?
How long till we can fly again?
有没有人能补一下这个枪子儿打穿的洞!
Somebody patch the other hole where the bullet came out!
给我  让我来吧
Give it to me.i'll do it.
快来这儿!  有没有人来帮忙加点油!  我去拿燃料
Here! somebody pump some gas! I'll handle the fuel.
把救生筏放下去!  快点!  我们走!
Get that life raft right there! come on! let's go!
Sun!
Hey, sun!
-Sun!  你去哪?  我们得走了  -Jin和Michael在下面  我不能...
- Sun! where you going? we gotta go. - jin's below with michael. I can't--
不行  没时间了!  没时间了  我们必须得走了
No, no, there's no time! there's no time. we have to go.
我不会丢下他的!
I won't leave him!
好  你把宝宝抱上直升机  我去找Jin
Okay. you get the baby on the chopper. I'll get jin.
-好吗?  -继续加油  直到我能发动起来!
- All right? - Just keep pumping till I get it started!
那样才够我们回到岛上
That'll be enough to get us to the island.
Jin  你必须得走
Jin, you gotta go.
-我们无能为力了  -不  我可以找到...
- There's nothing more we can do, man. - no, I can find--
快走  放弃吧  冷冻气几乎用尽了
Hey, come on. it's over. I'm almost out of this stuff.
听着  你现在是为人父的人了
Listen, you are a father now.
带着你的妻子回家
Get to your wife and get her home.
谢谢你  Michael
Thank you, michael.
不客气
You're welcome.
走
Go.
还没发动呢!
Hey! not yet!
你朋友三分钟前说过我们还有五分钟的
your buddy said we got five minutes as of three minutes ago.
如果你想走就快点  我们走了!  Kate!  快点!
If you're going, this is it. let's go! kate! come on!
Jin还在里面呢!
Jin's still inside!
-Jin还在里面  我们不能扔下他  -快点  听着
- Jin's still inside. we can't leave him behind. - come on. listen,
我不会丢下你不管的
I'm not leaving without you.
我们要离开这了  我们走!
We gotta get out of here now. let's go!
-再等等!  不要!  等等!  -Jin在哪?
- Give me a minute! no! wait! - where's jin?
是Jin!
It's jin!
Jin! Jin!
Jin! jin!
Jin!  我们必须回去!  调头!
Jin! we have to go back! turn around!
-不行  -回去!  我们必须回去!
- We can't do it! - we have to! we need to go back!
你现在可以脱身了  Michael
You can go now, michael.
你是谁?
Who are you?
Jin!
喂?
Hello?
你好!  有人想跟你说说话
Hello! Someone wants to talk to you!
向妈妈问声好  Ji Yeon
Say hello to your mother, Ji Yeon.
妈妈  妈妈
Mama. Mama.
你好啊  宝贝
Hello! My love!
你现在在哪?
Where are you?
我在伦敦  今晚就回去
I'm in London. I leave tonight.
只是有点生意要忙
Just finishing a little business.
路上小心
Fly safe.
好的  再见  妈妈
I will. Good-bye mother.
好的  伙计们  谢谢
All right, guys. thanks.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
你是Widmore先生吗?
Mr. widmore?
是的
Yes.
我是Sun Kwon  是Paik的女儿
I'm sun kwon... mr. paik's daughter.
我是Paik企业的常务董事
I'm the managing director of paik industries.
是的  我知道  你父亲可好?
Yes, of course. how is your father?
很好  谢谢
Excellent, thank you.
他高尔夫球打得很好
Quite the golfer.
我记得上次比赛后我还欠他一顿饭
I believe I owe him dinner after our last game.
你还真打算假装一直不认识我吗?
Are you really going to pretend that you don't know who I am?
我不明白你的意思  Kwon小姐
I'm afraid I don't know what you're talking about, ms. kwon.
你知道  你当然知道  Widmore先生
Yes, you do know, mr. widmore...
正如你知道
Just like you know
我们一直在隐瞒我们以前待的地方
We've been lying all this time about where we were
还有我们所遭遇的事
And what happened to us there.
你和我有着共同的利益驱使
You and I have common interests.
当你想要和我谈这些的时候
When you're ready to discuss them...
给我打电话
Call me.
正如你所知
As you know,
我们不是唯一离开那座岛的人
We're not the only ones who left the island.
Kwon小姐
Ms. kwon?
你为什么要帮助我?
Why would you want to help me?
飞回去!  我们一定要找到Jin!
Go back lower! we have to go find jin!
-Sun  那里已经没有人了!  -你怎么知道!
- Sun, there's nobody down there! - you can't see anything from here!
-油不够了!  我们不能回去!  -飞回去!  我知道他在那儿!
- We didn't get enough fuel! - we can't go back! go lower! I know he's there!
-Sun  我...Sun  我很抱歉  他已经...  -他在那里!
- Sun, I'm--sun, I'm so sorry. he's not-- - he's down there!
我知道他就在那里!
I know he's down there!
-我们得走了!  -不要!  我不要丢下他!
- We gotta go! - no! I'm not leaving him!
不能去找他!  不  我们不能丢下他!
Can't get to him! no, we're not leaving him!
不能!  快调头!
we're not! turn back around!
Sun!  sun!  他死了!
Sun! sun! it's gone!
他死了
He's gone.
嘘  嘘
Shh. shh.
Lapidus!
载我们回小岛
Fly us back to the island.
收到
You got it.
不!
No!
不!  不!
No! no!
不!
No!
为什么?
Why?
什么为什么?
"why" what?
你知道那东西能炸毁船  为什么还要杀死他?
Why did you kill him when you knew it would destroy the boat?
John  我当时真的难以控制我的情绪
Well, john, I really wasn't thinking straight.
有的时候...
Sometimes...
即使英明的决策
Good command decisions get compromised
也会受到不好的情绪所影响
By bad emotional responses.
我相信你能公私分明
I'm sure you're gonna do a much better job
比我做得更好
Of separating the two than I ever did.
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
-我在问你呢!  -如果我是你  我会躲一下
- I asked you a question! - if I were you, I'd duck.
我最好得改改了
I better change.
游泳的好天气啊
Nice day for a swim.
你还在这儿干嘛?
What are you doing here?
在想要不要去泡一泡
Decided to take a dip.
你在庆祝什么?
Whatcha celebratin'?
我没有在庆祝
I'm not celebrating.
那是我们的船吗?
Is that our boat?
曾经是
It was.
穿那个做什么?
What's that for?
我要去一个冰冷的地方
I'm going somewhere cold.
那我呢?
Then where is mine?
因为你不会和我一起去
Because you're not going with me.
-不  我会和你去的  -不会  John  你不会
- Yes, I am going with you.- no, john, you're not.
Jacob告诉过我要怎么做
Jacob told me what we had to do.
你不能就这样全权决定了...
You don't get to make all the decisions--
他告诉你要做什么  但没有跟你说怎么做
He told you what to do, but he didn't tell you how
-因为他要我来承担后果  -什么后果
- Because he wants me to suffer the consequences. - what consequences?
不管是谁移动了这岛就不会再活着出来
Whoever moves the island can never come back.
所以你得坐上电梯  John
So I'd like you to get on the elevator, john,
上去吧
And go back up.
Richard和我的人
Richard and my people will be waiting
-在兰花站西边2英里处等着  -等我?
- 2 miles east of the orchid. -  waiting for me?
他们愿意  乐意
Ready, willing and able
地告诉你他们所知道的事
To share what they know.
然后他们会对你马首是瞻
And then they will follow your every word.
再见  John
Good-bye, john.
很抱歉让你的生活如此痛苦
I'm sorry I made your life so miserable.
我要告诉他们做什么?
What do I tell 'em to do?
你会知道的  John
You'll find your way, john.
你向来如此
You always do.
你好  John
Hello, john.
欢迎回家
Welcome home.
我想你现在满意了吧  Jacob
I hope you're happy now, jacob.
那是什么?
Yeah, what is that?
岛去哪了?
Where's the island?
岛呢?
Where's the island?!
-他妈的 那岛哪去了?  -消失了
- Where the hell's the island?! - it's gone.
我把这鬼东西停哪儿啊?
Where the hell am I gonna land this thing?!
他们把我们带到过附近的另一个小一点的岛
There's another smaller island close by they took us to!
医生  我给你说
I got news for ya, doc!
四周除了水  什么也没有
There's nothing but water in every direction!
现在没关系了
Doesn't matter now.
我们完了  没油了
That's it, people! we're out of fuel!
穿上救生衣  我们要入水了
Get your life vests on! we're going in!
做好准备
Brace yourselves!
Desmond  救生筏
Desmond! the life raft!
坚持住
Hold on!
Jack呢?  Kate?  他去哪了?
Where's jack?! kate! where is he?!
你没事吧  hurley  抱着宝宝
Are you okay? hurley, carry the baby.
-Sayid  你没事吧?  -是的
- Sayid, are you all right?  - yes!
Jack  Desmond在哪?
Jack! where's desmond?
-抱着宝宝  -我接住它了
- Get the baby. - I got him.
Desmond
Desmond!
jack
Jack!
来搭把手
Give me a hand!
抓住你了
Here you go.
把他弄到救生筏上  把他放到救生筏上
Get him to the raft. get him to the raft.
把他放到救生筏上  得把他放到救生筏上
Get him up in the raft. we've gotta get him in the raft.
他还有呼吸吗?  天啊  他还有呼吸吗?
Is he breathing? oh, my god. is he breathing?
天啊
Oh, my god.
撑住  desmond
Oh, come on, desmond.
一  二  三
One, two, three.
好了
Yeah.
好了  好了
Yeah, yeah.
好了
Yeah.
好了  好了
Yeah. yeah.
好了  你没事了  你没事了  伙计
Yeah, you're all right. you're all right, man.
你没事了
You're okay.
desmond  你没事了
Desmond. that's it.
你没事了  没事了
You're all right. that's it.
没事了
It's okay.
我们还活着
We're alive.
喂?
Hello?
是谁?
Hello? who's there?
别动
Don't move.
别碰我儿子
Don't you touch my son!
Claire?
你怎么...
How did y--
别把他带回来  Kate
Don't bring him back, kate.
你怎么敢把他带回来
Don't you dare bring him back.
对不起
I'm sorry.
他还好吗?
Is he okay?
他没事
He's fine.
真是奇迹
It's a miracle.
我不敢相信他办到了
I can't believe he did it.
谁做了什么?
Who did what?
Locke
Locke.
他把岛移走了
He moved the island.
不  他没有
No, he didn't.
是吗?
Oh, really?
前一分钟那岛还在
Cause... one minute it was there,
接着就不见了  那么...
And the next it was gone, so...
伙计  除非是我们看花眼了
Unless we, like, overlooked it, dude,
这绝对是他做的
That's exactly what he did.
但是...如果你有另外的解释  伙计
But... if you've got another explanation, man,
我愿意洗耳恭听
I'd love to hear it.
万能的主啊
God almighty.
那有条船
There's a boat.
There's a boat out there!
那有条船  你看见了吗?
Hey! there's a boat! you see it?!
看呢  就在那
Hey! over here!
它看见我们了吗?  我想它看见了
Does it see us? I think it does!
它调头了?
It is turning?
它调头了!
It's turning! hey!
我们得撒谎
We're gonna have to lie.
什么?
What?
我们得撒谎
We're gonna have to lie.
撒什么谎?
Lie about what?
每一件事情  所有的事情
Everything, all of it,
我们坠机来到这个岛上之后的所有事
Every moment since we crashed on the island.
Jack...我虽然是刚刚才和你们一起
Jack... now I know I'm new to this group and everything,
但我觉得此时此地
But isn't this the place where everybody
-我们应该欢呼雀跃呀?  -你的货船...
- Starts jumping up and down and hugging each other?  - your freighter...
那些人来到岛上杀我们  我们所有人
Those men came to the island to kill us, all of us.
你说过我们的飞机被发现了
You said that our plane was discovered
在大洋底下
On the bottom of the ocean.
是有人把它放在那儿的...
Well, someone put it there--
而那个人想让所有的人都认为我们已经死了
Someone who wants everyone to think that we're dead.
那么你们认为当我们告诉世界那架飞机
So what do you think's gonna happen to us
不是我们乘坐的那架时会怎么样
When we tell them that that wasn't our plane?
而那些依然留在岛上的人
What do you think's gonna happen
又会怎样?
To the people that we left behind?
Jack  我们不能
Jack, we can't.
我们不能就这样全部忘记
We can't pull it off.
让我来说好了
Just let me do the talking.
下面有人!
Widmore女士  下面有艘救生筏
Widmore女士!
Ms. widmore!
把绳子扔给他们!  带他们去船尾!
Throw them a rope! take them 'round to the stern!
Penny?
Penny!
你还好吗?
Are you okay?
我...我很好
I'm--i'm fine.
我很好
I'm fine.
你怎么...怎么知道我的?
H-how did you find me?
你的电话...
Your phone call...
我有一个信号追踪站
I have a tracking station.
我爱你  Penny...
I love you, penny...
我再也不会离开你了
And I'll never leave you again.
这是...这是Penny
This is--this is penny.
-这是Kate和Aaron  -你好
- This is, um, kate and then aaron. - hi.
这是Sun
And this is sun,
Sayid  Hurley
Sayid, hurley.
你好
Hi.
这是Frank
This is frank.
还有Jack  Jack  这是...这是Penny
And jack. jack, this is--this is penny.
-很高兴见到你  Penny...  -你好
- It's nice to meet you, penny...  - hi.
不过我们得谈谈
But we need to talk.
一周后
One Week Later
这个地方叫什么?
What's this place called?
Membata
Membata.
我们为什么要这样做  伙计?
Why are we doing this, dude?
航行3000英里去另一个岛?
Sailing 3,000 miles to another island?
因为这是唯一让他们安全的办法
Because it's the only way to keep them safe.
-还有多久能靠岸?  -如果风不太猛烈的话...
- How long till we'll hit land?  - well, if the wind's not too brutal...
八九个小时吧
Eight, nine hours.
足够长来给你一个漂亮而且令人信服的晒斑
Just long enough to give you a nice, convincing sunburn.
这非常好  Frank
Well... it's been a pleasure, frank.
希望我们再也不会相见了
I hope we never see each other again.
收到  医生
Roger that, doc.
再见  小甜心
Bye, sweetheart.
你真的要这么做吗  兄弟?
Are you sure about this, brother?
你呢?
Are you sure?
只要能和Penny在一起...
As long as I've got penny...
我就没事
I'll be fine.
别让他找到你  Desmond
Don't let him find you, desmond.
我们来生再见吧  兄弟
I'll see you in another life, brother.
是的
Aye.
我猜你会的
I guess you will.
好吧
All right.
让我们回家吧
Let's go home.
尸体证明表
BODY RELEASE FORM
你好  Jack
Hello, jack.
抱歉
Sorry.
不是有意要吓你
Didn't mean to scare you.
他告诉你我离开了那个岛吗?
Did he tell you that I was off the island?
是的  告诉了
Yes, he did.
你什么时候跟他谈的话?
When did you speak to him?
大概一个月前
About a month ago.
Kate呢?
And kate?
是的
Yeah.
是的  他也来见她了
Yeah, he came to see her, too.
那他跟你说了些什么?
And what did he say to you?
他告诉我...
He told me...
我离开了那个岛之后
That after I left the island,
有些非常糟糕的事情发生了
Some very bad things happened.
他还告诉我那是我的错
And he told me that it was my fault
因为我的离去
For leaving.
他还说我得回去
And he said that I had to come back.
是的  我听说你经常搭乘客机...
Yes, I heard that you've been flying on passenger planes...
希望你会坠机
Hoping that you'd crash.
非常阴暗  Jack  非常阴暗
It's dark, jack, very dark.
你为什么在这儿?
Why are you here?
那个岛不会让你一个人回去的
That the island won't let you come alone.
你们所有的人都得回去
All of you have to go back.
你...
Are you...
Sayid...我都不知道Sayid在哪
Sayid--i don't even know where sayid is.
Hurley...
发疯了
Is insane.
Sun责怪我  因为...
Sun blames me for...
还有Kate...
And then kate...
她甚至都不再跟我说话了
She won't even talk to me anymore.
也许我能帮你
Perhaps I can help you with that.
你们必须得一起回去  Jack
This is the way it has to be, jack.
这是唯一的办法
It's the only way.
你们得一起  所有人
You have to do it together, all of you.
怎么做?
How?
我有些想法
I have a few ideas.
Jack...
我说过  你们所有人
I said, all of you.
我们还得把他也带上
We're gonna have to bring him, too.
==============| YYeTs字幕组招募启示 |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国) 双语字幕校正 时间轴调整
英语翻译 欧美影视新闻翻译 影视评论 论坛版主 美工人员
服务器提供者 发布宣传 联系地址：www.YYeTs.net
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报酬 ====